RG 005:036, Office of the Governor: Ella Grasso (1975-1980)
Connecticut State Library
Ella Grasso records
1971-1982
bulk, 1975-1980
1975-1980
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Governor (1975-1980: Grasso)
367.5 cubic feet
Includes correspondence, subject files, press releases, official statements, and speech files.
RG005_036
T001625
Biographical Note
Born: May 10, 1919, Windsor Locks, Connecticut.
College: Mount Holyoke College, Bachelor of Arts, 1940; Master of Arts, 1942.
Political Party: Democrat.
Offices: Connecticut House of Representatives, 1952-1957; Connecticut Secretary of the State, 1959-1971; U.S. Congress, 1971-1975; Governor of Connecticut, 1975-1980.
Died: February 5, 1981, Hartford, Connecticut.
The election of Ella Grasso in 1974 gave Connecticut its first female governor and its first governor of Italian heritage. Her election also gave the nation the first woman of any state to be elected governor in her own right, without having run on the record of a husband who had also been governor.
Born Ella Giovanna Oliva Tambussi, her parents James and Maria (Oliva) Tambussi were Italian immigrants who valued education highly and made it possible for her to attend private schools. She attended St. Mary's School, Windsor Locks, and the Chaffee School in Windsor and won a scholarship to Mount Holyoke College, where she received a B.A. in 1940 and an M.A. in economics and sociology in 1942. Convinced by her educational experiences that she should enter public service, Grasso served with Connecticut's War Manpower Commission during World War II. In 1942, she married Thomas Grasso. The couple had two children, Susanne and James.
Grasso's work for the Connecticut Democratic Party began in 1943. She was elected to Connecticut's House of Representatives from her hometown of Windsor Locks in 1952 and reelected in 1954, serving until 1957. Two years later she became Connecticut's Secretary of the State, holding that post for 12 years, longer than any Secretary of the State since 1835. In 1970, Grasso ran for the 6th Congressional District seat vacated by Republican Thomas Meskill, who was running for governor. She defeated Republican candidate Richard Kilborn in that election and was reelected in 1972. She served on the House Veterans' Affairs Committee and House Education and Labor Committee.
Accustomed to considerable influence in her home state, Grasso was frustrated with a system in Washington that left new legislators virtually powerless and by 1974 was receptive to the idea of challenging Meskill in the gubernatorial race. Her major opponent within the Democratic Party was Robert Killian of Hartford, the state's Attorney General, but Grasso's victory over Killian by a nearly 2,000-vote margin in the Hartford primary boosted her candidacy. Although her relationship with Killian was an uneasy one, as a unifying measure Grasso agreed to Democratic Party Chairman John Bailey's compromise plan to place Killian on the ticket as her running mate. Future governor William O'Neill served as her campaign manager. The Republicans nominated U.S. Representative Robert Steele, Jr. to oppose Grasso. Her victory, part of a complete sweep of the state by the Democrats that gave that party control of the General Assembly, set the stage for women like Madeleine Kunin of Vermont to assume the highest elected office available at the state level.
Ella Grasso took office in January of 1975 and almost immediately acquired the image of a "tough customer". Her records as governor demonstrate a hands-on approach to the administration of her office. She was a workaholic and expected her staff to perform with the same dedication and intensity; sometimes she would call the staff early in the morning to get them to the Capitol immediately for a meeting.
She initially faced problems similar to those that confronted Governor Meskill when he took office four years earlier. She inherited a seventy million dollar debt from the outgoing Meskill administration, forcing her to make some austere and unpopular moves. Without funding to carry out the social programs she had promised in her campaign, she chose to move slowly and offered only a few legislative programs during her first year in office. Legislation was passed to help consumers, and the Freedom of Information Act for Connecticut became law. The sales tax was raised to seven percent. Still the budget deficit grew, but, following the guidelines of Democratic Party Chairman John Bailey, she continued to oppose implementation of a state income tax. Grasso called a special session of the legislature in December 1975 and proposed tapping into the Veterans' Fund and requiring state employees to work more hours for the same pay. When the General Assembly refused to cooperate with her proposals, Grasso laid off 505 state employees just before Christmas. Her public image plummeted.
In 1976, Connecticut began its State Lottery. This, along with increases in the state's gasoline tax, an improved economy, and judicious use of state funds, finally gave Connecticut a budget surplus. As a result, most of the fired state employees were rehired. Ella Grasso still suffered from a negative image, but her ability to balance the budget, combined with increased aid to cities and towns and the reduction of some business taxes, improved public perceptions of her.
On the national political scene, Grasso's name was mentioned as a possible candidate for President or Vice President in the 1976 election. An early supporter of Henry "Scoop" Jackson, she saved herself considerable political embarrassment by switching her support to Jimmy Carter in June 1976. Grasso co-chaired the Democratic National Convention that July. Rumors circulated that Carter would name Grasso to his cabinet or as Ambassador to Italy, but Grasso had already announced her intention to run for another term as governor.
Grasso's popularity soared in February of 1978 when a huge blizzard hit Connecticut, paralyzing the state for days. Grasso went to the State Armory and took a personal interest in operations to help the citizens of Connecticut recover from the effects of the killer storm. The public now believed that it had not just a politician but a pro-active, caring, compassionate woman as governor. At the same time Grasso attempted to minimize Lieutenant Governor Robert Killian's political stock by not assigning him a substantive role during the crisis. That summer the Democrats nominated William A. O'Neill as their candidate for Lieutenant Governor on the ticket with Ella Grasso. Grasso's new image as "Mother Ella" helped her easily win reelection in 1978, defeating Republican challenger Ronald Sarasin by 189,000 votes. This huge victory was a testament to both her political shrewdness and her now immense appeal.
Grasso was in complete command at the beginning of her second term. Loyal Democrats controlled both houses. The large surplus continued, and she was able to increase social spending in some of the areas previously promised. Grasso's Urban Action Program directed funds to the needs of impoverished areas in the state, with money aimed at housing, mass transit, day care, and the elderly. However, the late 1970s were marked by an oil crisis that hurt the state's economy and required state aid for heating for the poor in the winter. This, and the increased operational costs of state government, forced Grasso to call for a tax increase for the first time in several years. Gasoline shortages in the summer of 1979 also tested her leadership abilities. A manageable system of odd/even rationing based on license plate number was instituted to ease hoarding and long lines. She opened an emergency gasoline center at the State Armory.
At the national level, Grasso was one of the first governors called to Camp David to discuss energy issues and was mentioned as a potential running mate in Carter's 1980 re-election campaign. But Connecticut's economic condition and Grasso's personal health both took a turn for the worse in 1980. Rising energy costs and increased unemployment contributed to a 128 million dollar revenue gap. Grasso had no choice but to call for an increase in the sales tax to seven and one half percent, one of the highest in the nation, as well as for increases in other taxes. In March she was diagnosed with cancer, and her condition worsened as the year progressed. Aware that her cancer was spreading, concerned about her service to the people of Connecticut, and feeling she was not able to function as governor in the way the people of Connecticut deserved, Grasso announced in early December that she would be resigning from office. Her resignation took effect on December 31, 1980, and Lt. Governor William O'Neill was immediately sworn in to replace her. Joseph Fauliso, President Pro Tempore of the Senate, took the oath as Lieutenant Governor.
Ella Grasso died at Hartford Hospital on February 5, 1981. Her body lay in state in the State Capitol for 24 hours, where she was mourned by the public and politicians of both parties. She was buried at St. Mary's Cemetery in Windsor Locks.
The people of Connecticut have honored Governor Grasso's contributions to the state in a number of ways. Streets in several Connecticut communities were named for her, including Ella Grasso Highway (Route 75) in Windsor Locks. State facilities in Groton and Stratford are named for her. Grasso received one of the highest honors that the State of Connecticut could bestow when a privately funded statue of her was placed in a niche above the south portico of the Capitol building. Only statues of Connecticut's most illustrious leaders are in the niches, and the statue of Ella Grasso was the first of a woman to be so placed.
Ella Tambussi Grasso's birthplace in Windsor Locks still stands, along with two houses she owned there. All are in private hands.
Bibliography
Bysiewicz, Susan. Ella: A Biography of Governor Ella Grasso. Old Saybrook, Conn.: Peregrine Press, 1984 [CSL call number F 101 .G7 B97 1984].
Chamberlin, Hope. A Minority of Members: Women in the United States Congress. New York: Prager Publishers, [1973] [CSL call number JK 1030 .A2 C5].
Congressional Quarterly's Guide to United States Elections. Washington, D.C.: Congressional Quarterly, 1994 [CSL call number GIS Ref JK 1967 .C662 1994.
Glashan, Roy R. American Governors and Gubernatorial Elections, 1775-1975. Stillwater, Minn.: Croixside Press, 1975 [CSL call number JK 2447 .G53 1975].
Janick, Herbert F. A Diverse People: Connecticut, 1914 to the Present. Chester, Conn.: Pequot Press, c1975 [CSL call number HistRef Conn Doc St22eacs v. 5].
Lieberman, Joseph. The Legacy, Connecticut Politics, 1930-1980 Hartford, Conn.: Spoonwood Press, 1981 [CSL call number JK 3395 .L53 1981].
Sobel, Robert and John Raimo. Biographical Directory of the Governors of the United States, 1789-1978. Westport, Conn.: Meckler Books, 1978 [CSL call number GIS Ref E 176 .B573].
Scope and Content
Includes correspondence, subject files, press releases, official statements, and speech files. Files from Gov. O'Neill's administration are also included as are files that may have been carried over from the Meskill administration to ensure continuity of executive actions.
Arrangement
Arrangement is in parts conforming to successive transfers of files from the Governor's Office.
Part I Subject Files, 1972-1977.
Part II Subject Files, 1971-1980.
Part III Subject Files, 1974-1981.
Part IV Subject Files, 1971-1982.
Part V Subject Files, 1974-1981.
Part VI Subject Files, 1979-1981.
Part VII Supplementary Files, 1971-1980.
Inclusive dates of the seven parts overlap and contain similar subject files.
Researchers are advised to consult all seven parts for materials covering specific topics or periods of time. Also, searching for a particular subject may require a review of numerous file headings. For example, information on wife or child abuse may be alphabetical under those headings, or as a subheading of "Legislation," or filed under a particular state agency.
Related Material
PG 500, Individual and Family Portrait Collection.
PG 560, Connecticut Group Portraits.
Index Terms
Persons:
Grasso, Ella
Subjects:
Grasso, Ella -- Archives; Connecticut. Office of the Governor -- Archives; Connecticut -- History -- Sources; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- 1951- -- Sources; Governors -- Connecticut -- Archives; Women governors -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Clippings; Correspondence; Photographs; Press releases; Proclamations; Records; Reports; Speeches
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
Boxes 223, 224, 225, 473, and 558 related to Mental Health were known to contain documents with confidential personal information. The original documents have been removed and replaced with redacted copies. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
See the policy.
Container List
- Part I Subject Files, 1972-1977
  The code in parentheses denotes whether correspondence in the files is incoming (I), outgoing (O) or Both (B).
  - Abortion (Box 1)
    - A (B) (Box 1)
    - Letters answered by postcard (I) (Box 1)
    - Letter to printed (I) (Box 1)
    - Letter #31 Revised (B), 1977 July 25 (Box 1)
    - Petitions (O) (Box 1)
    - Petition answered by postcard (B) (Box 1)
    - Petition answered by postcard, 1977 August (Box 1)
    - Platform Plak (B) (Box 1)
    - Support letters A-F (B) (Box 1)
    - Support letters G-L (Box 1)
    - Support letters M-Z (B) (Box 2)
    - Write-up (Box 2)
    - #31 Revised (Box 2)
    - 31B Printed Letter (Box 2)
    - 31C Printed Letter (Box 2)
  - Accomplishments (Box 2)
  - Accountants (B) (Box 2)
  - Acknowledgments (B) (Box 2)
    - A (B) (Box 2)
    - Ba (B) (Box 2)
    - Be-Bi (B) (Box 3)
    - Bl-Bo (B) (Box 3)
    - Br-Bz (B) (Box 3)
    - Ca (B) (Box 4)
    - Cc-Con (B) (Box 4)
    - Coo-Cz (B) (Box 5)
    - D (B) (Box 5)
    - E (B) (Box 6)
    - Fa-Fo (B) (Box 6)
    - Fr-Fz (B) (Box 6)
    - Ga-Gr (B) (Box 7)
    - Gl-Gz (B) (Box 7)
    - H (B) (Box 8)
    - I-J (B) (Box 8)
    - K (B) (Box 9)
    - L (B) (Box 10)
    - Ma (B) (Box 11)
    - Mc-Me (B) (Box 11)
    - Mi-Mz (B) (Box 11)
    - N-O (B) (Box 12)
    - P (B) (Box 12)
    - Q-R (B) (Box 13)
    - SA (B) (Box 13)
    - Sc-Se (B) (Box 14)
    - Sh-Sl (B) (Box 14)
    - Sm-Sp (B) (Box 14)
    - St-Sz (B) (Box 15)
    - T (B) (Box 15)
    - U-V (B) (Box 15)
    - Wa-We (B) (Box 16)
    - Wh-Wi (B) (Box 16)
    - Wn-Wz (B) (Box 16)
    - XYZ (B) (Box 16)
  - Acknowledgments (Box 17)
    - Referral #17B (Jeremy) (B) (Box 17)
    - Referral #34a (B) (Box 18)
    - 34b (Sent to Milano for response) (office of Policy and Management) (B) (Box 18)
    - 34b (B) (Box 18)
  - Action (B) (Box 18)
  - Administrative Services, Dept. of Aetna World Cup (B) (Box 18)
  - Aetna World Cup (Box 18)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 18)
  - Age of Majority (Box 18)
  - Aging (Box 19)
    - A (B) (Box 19)
    - B (B) (Box 19)
    - C (B) (Box 19)
    - D (B) (Box 19)
    - E (B) (Box 19)
    - F (B) (Box 19)
    - G (B) (Box 19)
    - H (B) (Box 20)
    - I, J (B) (Box 20)
    - K (B) (Box 20)
    - L (B) (Box 20)
    - M (B) (Box 20)
    - N (B) (Box 20)
    - O-P (B) (Box 20)
    - Q-R (B) (Box 20)
    - S (B) (Box 21)
    - T (B) (Box 21)
    - UVW (B) (Box 21)
    - XYZ (B) (Box 21)
  - Aging (Box 21)
    - Advisory Council on Aging: (B) (Box 21)
    - Breakthrough to the Estuary and mid-state Region (B) (Box 21)
    - dept. on, #48, 1977 March 8 (Box 21)
    - Landmark Square (I) (Box 21)
    - Letters to People being Replaced on Advisory Council on Aging (O) (Box 21)
    - Minority Elderly Action Team (O) (Box 21)
    - Misc. Material (Box 21)
    - New Clippings (Box 21)
    - 1975 Legislative Proposals (Box 21)
    - Nutrition for - Pfeiffer (B) (Box 21)
    - Dept. on, #48 (B), 1977 March 8 (Box 21)
    - Pre-Retirement (B) (Box 21)
    - Press Releases (Box 21)
    - Press Release from Governor’s office (Box 21)
    - Project STEP (B) (Box 21)
  - Project Triage #5 (B), 1977 September (Box 22)
    - Reports to General Assembly (Box 22)
    - Senior Intern Program (Box 22)
    - State Plan on, 1977 (Box 22)
    - State plan on, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Title XX (Box 22)
  - [Agriculture] (Box 22)
    - Pro Wilbur (B) (Box 22)
  - Agriculture (Box 22)
    - A, B (B) (Box 22)
    - C, D (B) (Box 22)
    - E, F (B) (Box 22)
    - G, H (B) (Box 22)
    - I, J (B) (Box 22)
    - K, L (B) (Box 22)
    - M, N (B) (Box 22)
    - O, P (B) (Box 22)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 22)
    - S, T (B) (Box 23)
    - U, V, W (B) (Box 23)
    - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 23)
  - Agriculture (Box 23)
    - Aquaculture (Box 23)
    - Board of (O) (Box 23)
    - Case-Collins (B) (Box 23)
    - Case - Hunt (B) (Box 23)
    - Connecticut Citizens for Food and Agriculture (Box 23)
    - Closed (B) (Box 23)
    - Experimental Station (I) (Box 23)
    - Food Distribution (O) (Box 23)
    - Future Farmers of America (B) (Box 23)
    - Humane Treatment of Horses Transported into Connecticut (B) (Box 23)
    - Land Use (B) (Box 23)
    - Milk Regulation Board (O) (Box 23)
    - Misc. Information (Box 23)
    - Misc. Material (Box 23)
    - press Releases from Governor’s Office (Box 23)
    - Stabilization and Conservation Service, Annual Reports (B) (Box 23)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 23)
    - Yankee Milk News (Box 23)
  - Alaska pipeline (B) (Box 23)
  - Alcohol (ICS and Programs) (B) (Box 23)
  - Alcohol
    - Advisory Council (B) (Box 24)
    - State Alcohol and Drug Council (Box 24)
    - State Alcohol Council (B) (Box 24)
  - Alcoholism (Box 24)
    - A, B (B) (Box 24)
    - C, D (B) (Box 24)
    - E, F (B) (Box 24)
    - G, H (B) (Box 24)
    - I, J, K (B) (Box 24)
    - L, M (B) (Box 24)
    - N, O (B) (Box 24)
    - P, Q (B) (Box 24)
    - R, S (B) (Box 24)
    - T, U, V (B) (Box 24)
    - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 24)
  - Alcoholism (Box 24)
    - Misc. Material (Box 24)
    - Prevention & Treatment (Box 24)
    - Shirley Frank Foundation (B) (Box 24)
  - Aliens (B) (Box 24)
  - All-American Teenager Pageant (Box 24)
  - Allegheny Airlines - Press Releases (Box 24)
  - Ambulance (B) (Box 24)
  - American Banker (Box 24)
  - American & Francophone Commission (B) (Box 24)
  - American Institute (Box 24)
  - American Mothers Committee (B) (Box 24)
  - American Security Council (Box 24)
  - Amnesty Week (B) (Box 24)
  - Animals (B) (Box 24)
  - Annual Reports (B) (Box 25)
  - Appointments (Box 25)
    - A-C (O) (Box 25)
    - D-F (O) (Box 25)
    - G-I (O) (Box 25)
    - J-L (O) (Box 25)
    - M-O (O) (Box 26)
    - P-R (O) (Box 26)
    - S-U (O) (Box 26)
    - V-Z (O) (Box 26)
  - [Appointments] (Box 26)
    - J. Blair - School Fin. (O) (Box 26)
  - Appointments (Box 26)
  - Appreciation (O) (Box 26)
  - Appropriations (B) (Box 26)
  - Appropriations Committee (Box 26)
  - Arbitrators (B) (Box 26)
  - Architecture (Box 26)
  - Architectural Registration Board (B) (Box 26)
  - Architectural & Transportation Barriers Compliance Board (Box 26)
  - Arts (B) (Box 26)
    - A,B (Box 26)
    - C, D (B) (Box 27)
    - E, F (B) (Box 27)
    - G, H (B) (Box 27)
    - I, J (B) (Box 27)
    - K, L (B) (Box 27)
    - M, N (B) (Box 27)
    - O, P (B) (Box 27)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 27)
    - S, T (B) (Box 27)
    - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 27)
  - Art Commission Appointments (Box 27)
  - Arts Commission - Office & Printed Letter (I), 1975 March (Box 27)
  - Arts Commission - Letters, Grants (Box 27)
  - Art Grants (Box 28)
  - Arts Commission - Press releases (Box 28)
  - Art Foundation (B) (Box 28)
  - Art Foundation Grant: (Box 28)
  - Art Foundation Grant Recipients (Box 28)
  - Art Jobs (O) (Box 28)
  - Art - Misc. Material (Box 28)
  - Article (B) (Box 28)
  - Article on the Governor (Box 28)
  - Atomic energy Commission (Box 28)
  - Attorney General (Box 28)
    - A, B, C (B) (Box 28)
    - D, E, F (B) (Box 28)
    - G, H, I (B) (Box 28)
    - J, K, L (B) (Box 28)
    - M, N, O (B) (Box 28)
    - P, Q, R (B) (Box 28)
    - S, T (B) (Box 28)
    - U, V (B) (Box 28)
  - Auctioneers (B) (Box 28)
  - Audition (B) (Box 28)
  - Auditors (Box 29)
  - Auditors - Letters (B) (Box 29)
  - Auditors of Public Accountants - Mags #11 & 11a (Box 29)
  - Audrey Beck (Box 29)
  - Australia (Box 29)
  - Autism (Box 29)
  - Autographs: (Box 29)
    - A-L (I) (Box 29)
    - M-Z (I) (Box 29)
  - Awards (Box 30)
  - Bailey (Box 30)
  - Bakers Association (Box 30)
  - Banking (Box 30)
    - A, B (Box 30)
    - C, D (Box 30)
    - E, F (Box 30)
    - G, H (Box 30)
    - k, L (Box 30)
    - M, N (Box 30)
    - O, P (Box 30)
    - Q, R (Box 30)
    - S, T (Box 30)
    - X, Y, Z (Box 30)
  - Banking - Misc. Material (Box 30)
  - Banking - Permanent Releases from Governor’s office (Box 30)
  - Banking Law - Advisory Committee to Study Reconciliation of (Box 30)
  - Barbers, Board of Examiners (B) (Box 31)
  - Bayh (B) (Box 31)
  - Better Business Bureau (Box 31)
  - Bicentennial (Box 31)
    - A (B) (Box 31)
    - B (Box 31)
    - C (Box 31)
    - D (Box 31)
    - E (Box 31)
    - F (Box 31)
    - G (Box 31)
    - H (B) (Box 32)
    - I, J (B) (Box 32)
    - K (B) (Box 32)
    - L (B) (Box 32)
    - M (B) (Box 32)
    - N (B) (Box 32)
    - O (B) (Box 32)
    - P (B) (Box 32)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 32)
    - T (B) (Box 32)
    - U, V (B) (Box 33)
    - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 33)
  - Bicentennial Gazette (Box 33)
  - Bicentennial - Louisiana Territory or Lewis & Clark Lost & Found (Box 33)
  - Bicentennial - Misc.. Material (Box 33)
  - Biography (Box 33)
  - Black Democrats (B) (Box 33)
  - Black Silent Majority (Box 33)
  - Black Safety Board (Box 33)
  - Bond Commission (Box 33)
  - [Bond Commission - State] - untitled folder (Box 33)
  - Bond Commission - Minutes & Agenda (Box 33)
    - Minutes, 1976 May 28 (Box 34)
    - Agenda, 1976 June 25 (Box 34)
    - Minutes, 1976 June 25 (Box 34)
    - Agenda, 1976 July 23 (Box 34)
    - Minutes, 1976 August 27 (Box 34)
    - Agenda, 1976 September 17 (Box 34)
    - Minutes, 1977 July 21 (Box 35)
    - Agenda, 1977 August 25 (Box 35)
  - Bond Misc. Material (Box 35)
  - Boy Scouts (B) (Box 35)
  - Bridgeport & Office (B) (Box 35)
  - Budget (Box 35)
    - A, B (B) (Box 35)
    - C, D (B) (Box 35)
    - E, F (B) (Box 35)
    - G, H (B) (Box 35)
    - I, J (B) (Box 35)
    - K, L (B) (Box 35)
    - M, N (B) (Box 35)
    - O, P (B) (Box 35)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 36)
    - S, T (B) (Box 36)
    - U, V, W (B) (Box 36)
    - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 36)
  - Budget (Box 36)
    - General Assembly (O) (Box 36)
    - General Assembly (O), 1977-1978 (Box 36)
  - Budget hearings (Box 36)
    - Letters to chief elected official (Box 36)
    - Letter to Comm.., 1977 November 17 (Box 36)
    - Leaders (Box 36)
  - Budget (Box 36)
    - Invitations to Special budget Hearings for Municipal officials/First Selectman/Mayors (O) (Box 36)
  - Budget (Box 36)
    - Letters (O) (Box 36)
  - Budget Letters (I), 1975 May (Box 36)
  - Budget Letters (New) (B), 1975 August 8 (Box 36)
  - Budget Letters #6 (B) (Box 36)
  - Budget Letters 6A to State Employees (B) (Box 36)
  - Budget Letters 6B sent to non-state employees (B) (Box 37)
  - Budget Letters 6C (B) (Box 37)
  - [Budget] (Box 37)
    - Memo’s to or from Conkling (Box 37)
  - Budget Message Request (O) (Box 37)
  - Budget Miscellaneous (Box 37)
  - Budget Surplus (B) (Box 37)
  - Budget (State) Surplus #7 (B) (Box 37)
  - Budget Surplus (Box 37)
    - New - Mag. #7 (B) (Box 37)
  - Budget Surplus (Box 37)
    - Mag. #7 (B) (Box 37)
  - Budgets (Box 37)
    - Tentative (Box 37)
  - Building Inspector (State) (Box 38)
    - Code Standards (B) (Box 38)
  - Bureau of Census (Box 38)
  - Bureau of Census (U.S) (Box 38)
    - Conference (O) (Box 38)
  - Bureau of Census (U.S.) TX’s for Attending Conference (O) (Box 38)
  - Bureau of Support (B) (Box 38)
  - Business (B) (Box 38)
  - Business (Box 38)
    - Closed (Box 38)